George Beck Papers
George Beck Papers
1950-1969
Beck, George A., 1908-1977.
24.5 linear ft.
American industrial designer. Collection includes notes, drawings, correspondence, reports, conference materials, public relations and marketing material, product data, slides, transparencies, models, and much more.
2750907
Biographical History
George A. Beck (1908-1977) was an American industrial designer. He first worked for Montgomery Ward and then Sears Roebuck, but the majority of his career (more than thirty years, starting in 1934) was spent with General Electric
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The George Beck Papers includes notes, drawings, correspondence, reports, conference materials, public relations and marketing material, product data, slides, transparencies, models, and much more.
The collection has received minimal processing. The inventory that follows is a simple box list, and folders retain Beck's original labels and are in no particular order. Researchers are advised to read the entire inventory to ensure locating all relevant materials.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection has received minimal processing and remains in original order.
Related Material
has the papers of many noted industrial designers. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Industrial Design; Beck, George A., 1908-1977.; General Electric Company.; Industrial Designers Society of America.; Industrial design -- United States.; Industrial designers -- United States.; Brochures.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Drawings (visual works); Photographs.; Reports.; Research notes.; Slides (photographs); Industrial designers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Transfer from University Archives, 2000.
Inventory
- Box 7079
  - 'Fortune' article; nation & its industry in space 'industrial design', March 1961 (Box 7079)
  - Fires in high-rise buildings (Box 7079)
  - Executive weekly day-timer (Arthur's) (Box 7079)
  - Weekly day-timer (George beck associates) (Box 7079)
  - Weekly day-timer, Oct 1970 - Oct 1971 (Box 7079)
  - Oberdorfer pump renderings (Box 7079)
  - GAB folder (Box 7079)
  - Telemax drawings (Box 7079)
- Box 7080
  - Air conditioner (Box 7080)
  - Ash tray & humidor (Box 7080)
  - Automobile design (Box 7080)
  - Bissel (Box 7080)
  - Boats (Box 7080)
  - Beverage cooler (Box 7080)
  - Escutcheon (Box 7080)
  - Dishwasher (Box 7080)
  - Dictaphone (Box 7080)
  - Correspondence (Box 7080)
  - Casco (Box 7080)
  - Boat (Box 7080)
  - Fans (Box 7080)
  - Perspective (Box 7080)
  - Photostat (Box 7080)
  - Radio-auto (Box 7080)
  - Radio-prints (Box 7080)
  - Metal, silverware, glassware, ceramic, plastics (Box 7080)
  - Displays (Box 7080)
  - Chicago (Box 7080)
  - Refrigerator hard prints (Box 7080)
  - Range hard prints (Box 7080)
  - Ranges (Box 7080)
  - General (Box 7080)
  - Cartoon (Box 7080)
  - Renderings
    - Interiors (Box 7080)
    - Gold/brass/chrome smokador (Box 7080)
    - Advertising & sketches (Box 7080)
    - Booklets & competition (Box 7080)
    - Tables, etc. (Box 7080)
    - Stands & trays (Box 7080)
    - Full-size (Box 7080)
    - Tables ash tray (Box 7080)
  - Design, pencil (Box 7080)
  - Rendering, color (Box 7080)
  - Refrig. nameplate paints (Box 7080)
  - Toasters (Box 7080)
  - Thermo guide humidity ind. (Box 7080)
  - To do (Box 7080)
  - Smokador
    - Color stock Baylis co. (Box 7080)
    - Color (Box 7080)
    - Displays (Box 7080)
    - Wall-type ashtray (Box 7080)
  - Ornament, empire design (Box 7080)
  - Oil burner (Box 7080)
  - Nameplates-labels (Box 7080)
  - Murals (Box 7080)
  - Kitchen (Box 7080)
  - Laundry (Box 7080)
  - Radio (Box 7080)
  - Comments by clients (Box 7080)
  - Gamble company, radio designs & photos (Box 7080)
  - Certificates (Box 7080)
  - Jerrold
    - Electric convertor (Box 7080)
    - RCU wall hanger (Box 7080)
    - RCU unit (Box 7080)
    - TV convertor (Box 7080)
    - SDS 1 (Box 7080)
    - Keyboard unit (Box 7080)
    - RCU artwork (Box 7080)
    - Bernzomatic gas grill re-do (Box 7080)
    - G.B. XLT brochures (Box 7080)
    - Eagan-Fairmount (Box 7080)
    - Raytheon range graphics (Box 7080)
    - G.B. brochures
      - General (Box 7080)
      - 1973 (Box 7080)
    - GAB corporate I.D., 1972 (Box 7080)
    - Manlius Liquors (Box 7080)
    - Metropolitan Development Association, 1972 (Box 7080)
    - Oneida
      - Stainless storage (Box 7080)
      - Melamine merchandising display (Box 7080)
      - Display, 8/28/72 (Box 7080)
      - Des. dev. sketches, 12/20/71 (Box 7080)
      - Solid stainless display, 12/71 (Box 7080)
      - Lysander new community models, 3/25/71 (Box 7080)
- Box 7081
  - New contracts
    - Agway (Box 7081)
    - Arthur's (Box 7081)
    - Morris Kopelove (Box 7081)
    - Alcoa (Box 7081)
    - Albert's (Box 7081)
    - Albert's graphics (Box 7081)
    - Barton Aschiman (Box 7081)
    - Brian (Box 7081)
    - New community Baldwinsville, Lysander (Box 7081)
    - World buttery (Box 7081)
    - Buttery menu panel (Box 7081)
    - Cazenovia College (Box 7081)
    - J. Van Heusen award dinner (Box 7081)
    - Charles Gourmet (Box 7081)
    - Digney, Marion (Box 7081)
    - Eagan models (Box 7081)
    - Ekblau (Box 7081)
    - Faxton (Box 7081)
    - 5 to 9 (Box 7081)
    - Foamold, 2 folders (Box 7081)
    - Pure fluid devices (Box 7081)
    - Ziaia (Box 7081)
    - G.E. dining\Hommel (Box 7081)
    - Kopp (Box 7081)
    - Lincoln Bank, money market signs (Box 7081)
    - Color sample (Box 7081)
    - Lincoln Bank (Box 7081)
    - Magnavox (Box 7081)
    - Maxson
      - General (Box 7081)
      - Telemax (Box 7081)
    - Telemax colors (Box 7081)
    - Maxson
      - Fone-Fax (Box 7081)
      - Related materials (Box 7081)
    - Root & Clark. OCC (Box 7081)
  - Hueber/Le Moyne (Box 7081)
  - King & King (Box 7081)
  - Auburn (Box 7081)
  - Models (Box 7081)
  - MDA; Un. Hill renovation & cube minibus, 12/69 (Box 7081)
  - Stevens, Burton, O'Connell (Box 7081)
  - Onondaga Bank (Box 7081)
  - Marine pump (Box 7081)
  - Oberdorfer
    - General (Box 7081)
    - Pump division (Box 7081)
    - Market survey (Box 7081)
  - Presidential plaza
    - Correspondence (Box 7081)
    - Medical center (Box 7081)
    - Beck's 1201-sch i (Box 7081)
  - Raytheon (Box 7081)
  - Sako
    - Finland (Box 7081)
    - Correspondence, notes (Box 7081)
    - Trip (Box 7081)
    - Sketches (Box 7081)
  - Juhani, Feb 1970 (Box 7081)
  - Sutton re Co. (Box 7081)
  - Syroco (Box 7081)
  - Syracuse, housing, city planning, UDC, MDA (Box 7081)
  - Syracuse Press Club (Box 7081)
  - University Hill GNRP, illus. site plan scale 1"-80' (Box 7081)
  - United Parcel Service (Box 7081)
  - H. Ward (Box 7081)
  - H.P.C. Hamilton Publishing Co. (Box 7081)
  - F.M.
    - Corridors & lobby (Box 7081)
    - Colors, Manlius Elem. (Box 7081)
    - Corridor & lobby (Box 7081)
    - School (Box 7081)
    - Classroom (Box 7081)
  - Assoc. (Box 7081)
  - GAB assoc. (Box 7081)
  - University Club of Syr. (Box 7081)
  - F.M. Curtis' office (Box 7081)
  - Flight service (Box 7081)
  - Sibley's proposal (Box 7081)
  - Office personnel & organization (Box 7081)
  - Budget, 1956 (Box 7081)
  - Administrative committee (Box 7081)
  - Budget
    - [Miscellaneous], 1951-1952 (Box 7081)
    - General (Box 7081)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1944-1948; 5 folders (Box 7081)
  - Scroll, Hazeltine data display control (Box 7081)
- Box 11799
  - ICSID, 1963-1967; 6 folders (Box 11799)
  - Sketches (Box 11799)
  - Notebooks, general notes (Box 11799)
  - Drawings (Box 11799)
  - Personal, 1951-1953; 3 folders (Box 11799)
  - President (Box 11799)
  - Personal and personnel letter book, 1948 (Box 11799)
  - Personal, 1950 (Box 11799)
  - Personal and personnel letter book, 1951-1952; 2 folders (Box 11799)
  - Personal, 1943-1947 (Box 11799)
  - G.E., radios and radio-phonographs, 1942; presentation notebooks (Box 11799)
  - Appliance and merchandising department, appearance design (Box 11799)
  - G.E. marketing plans, 1956 (Box 11799)
  - G.E. cabinet data (Box 11799)
  - Combinations, cabinet drawings (Box 11799)
- Box 11800
  - General Electric
    - LMEE Johnson City (Box 11800)
    - Light military, sales promotion (Box 11800)
    - LMED office (Box 11800)
    - Missiles (Box 11800)
    - Representative sheets (Box 11800)
    - Capacitor department (Box 11800)
    - Military electronics, 1,2, & 3 (Box 11800)
    - Radio and tv color proofs (Box 11800)
    - Washington headquarters (Box 11800)
    - Graphics and packaging (Box 11800)
    - Transmitter, mikes (Box 11800)
  - Industrial design organizational plans, 1958 (Box 11800)
  - ICSID (Box 11800)
  - IDI (Box 11800)
  - Photos of hill (Box 11800)
  - MDA (Box 11800)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 11800)
  - Negatives (Box 11800)
  - Oneida silver (Box 11800)
  - Optical display unit (Box 11800)
  - Presidential plaza (Box 11800)
  - Raytheon (Box 11800)
  - Telemax, Mason (Box 11800)
  - Sako (Box 11800)
  - Wescon (Box 11800)
- Box 11801
  - IDSA Detroit, 1967 (Box 11801)
  - George Beck, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 11801)
  - IDSA administration, ethics, policy and re. correspondence (Box 11801)
  - Certification (Box 11801)
  - Miscellaneous committees and reports (Box 11801)
  - Education survey and council (Box 11801)
  - Executive committee, and board of directors minutes, reports, budgets (Box 11801)
  - Membership rosters, IDSA directory, 1969 (Box 11801)
  - IDSA membership (Box 11801)
  - IDSA publications (Box 11801)
  - Safety council (Box 11801)
  - IDSA surveys (Box 11801)
  - IDSA 'design notes' publication (Box 11801)
  - IDI correspondence, 1964 (Box 11801)
  - IDI 'date line' and miscellaneous publications (Box 11801)
  - IDI educational programs, 1963 (Box 11801)
  - IDI/ASID inter-society committee (merger) (Box 11801)
  - ASID/IDI 1964 (Box 11801)
  - ICSID
    - News bulletins (Box 11801)
    - Addresses (Box 11801)
    - Constitution, codes, resolutions, policy, ethics (Box 11801)
    - 1957-1960, 4 folders (Box 11801)
    - Paris, 1963 (Box 11801)
- Box 11802
  - GAB comment (Box 11802)
  - General Electric, Bridgeport (Box 11802)
  - Locomotives (Box 11802)
  - Portraits (Box 11802)
  - G.B. graphics, 11/69; letterheads, cards, etc. (Box 11802)
  - G.B. stationery (Box 11802)
  - G.B. graphics (Box 11802)
  - Graphics completed (Box 11802)
  - Caz college IDSA (Box 11802)
  - ICSID Ibiza (International Conference of Industrial Designers), 1971 (Box 11802)
  - Administration, general (Box 11802)
  - Wescon, 1962 (Box 11802)
  - Syracuse University (Box 11802)
  - Talk speeches (Box 11802)
  - Administration, speeches/papers (Box 11802)
  - LMEE, talks and speeches (Box 11802)
  - ID/articles/speeches, art center (Box 11802)
  - Syr, March 1976 (Box 11802)
  - Conference leadership (Box 11802)
  - Creativity as a process (Box 11802)
- Box 11803
  - P.R. materials and promotion (Box 11803)
  - Design critique (Box 11803)
  - Limelight and various newsletters (Box 11803)
  - Merger (Box 11803)
  - News clippings (Box 11803)
  - Correspondence (Box 11803)
  - IDSA publications (Box 11803)
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 11803)
  - General Electric portfolios (Box 11803)
  - L.M.M. Correspondence (Box 11803)
  - L.B. 3rd floor (Box 11803)
  - L.B. Minoa letters (Box 11803)
  - Monroe building, Costello, Cooney and Fearon (Box 11803)
  - L.B. Minoa sketches (Box 11803)
  - Albert's sketches (Box 11803)
  - White Towers, Washington (Box 11803)
  - Foamold brochure (Box 11803)
  - G.E. Intercom (Box 11803)
  - Glass frame display, Hommel (Box 11803)
  - Everson Museum (Box 11803)
  - Everson Museum information (Box 11803)
  - Eagan display table (Box 11803)
  - D.C.P. (Box 11803)
  - Kiosk (Box 11803)
  - Vanderbilt square signs (Box 11803)
  - Nebs, point of sale signs (Box 11803)
  - Chamber of commerce award (Box 11803)
  - 1881 chest, Oneida ltd. (Box 11803)
  - Oneida silver, combination tv/ware tray (Box 11803)
  - Oneida ltd., melamine trays (Box 11803)
  - Oneida r & d (Box 11803)
  - U.N. Club (Box 11803)
  - George reprints (Box 11803)
  - Resume, G. Beck (Box 11803)
  - Miscellaneous published materials (Box 11803)
  - Slides (Box 11803)
- Box 11804
  - A-G (Box 11804)
  - Anderson and Pickard (Box 11804)
  - Bernzomatic, color flame (Box 11804)
  - Bernzomatic, ceramic grill (Box 11804)
  - Bernzomatic development (Box 11804)
  - Bernzomatic annual report, 1971 (Box 11804)
  - CGT and Associates Inc. (communication growth technology) (Box 11804)
  - Car bumpers (Box 11804)
  - Eagan signs, 2/71 (Box 11804)
  - Eagan plaque (Box 11804)
  - Eagan/Kemper, 1968-1970 (Box 11804)
  - Kemper Eagan real estate (Box 11804)
  - Jerrold Electronics SDS keyboard encoder, 1974 (Box 11804)
  - Jerrold, Sep 1974; Oct-Jan 1975 (Box 11804)
    - Annual report (Box 11804)
    - ADTSG and compet (Box 11804)
    - To do (Box 11804)
    - 1974, Jan-Aug, 7 folders (Box 11804)
    - 1973, Mar-May, 4 folders (Box 11804)
    - Electronics, 1973 (Box 11804)
    - Oprints, 1973 (Box 11804)
    - Electronics, 1972 (Box 11804)
  - Kennedy Memorial (Box 11804)
  - Manlius Liquor Store (Box 11804)
  - Magnavox (Box 11804)
  - Ober-bull sketches (Box 11804)
  - PPS bulletin (Box 11804)
  - IDI, 1963 (Box 11804)
  - Oak Park High School Journal (Box 11804)
  - J. Van Heusen display (Box 11804)
  - The Rochester Story (Box 11804)
  - Design concepts (Box 11804)
  - Office product sketches (Box 11804)
  - Lincoln Bank/MONY (Box 11804)
  - Microelectronics symbol (Box 11804)
  - Foamold (Box 11804)
  - Graphics (Box 11804)
- Box 11805
  - Syracuse, new bldg., 1980 (Box 11805)
  - Syracuse, model update, 1980 (Box 11805)
  - King, Syracuse U. Library (Box 11805)
  - Auburn city model (Box 11805)
  - Comm. College (Box 11805)
  - MDA directory (Box 11805)
  - Central Syracuse display (Box 11805)
  - Upstate (Box 11805)
  - University Hill model (Box 11805)
  - University Hill display (Box 11805)
  - U. Hill corporation photos (Box 11805)
  - Old university hill area building drawings (Box 11805)
  - King and King (Box 11805)
  - Bristol sketches (Box 11805)
  - Brach. model Syracuse (Box 11805)
  - Pres. Plaza apt.
    - Sketches (Box 11805)
    - Letters (Box 11805)
    - Notes (Box 11805)
    - Fountain (Box 11805)
    - Holstein space (Box 11805)
    - Sec'ty service space (Box 11805)
  - Onon. Community College (Box 11805)
  - Arthur's King of beef (Box 11805)
  - Arthur's time study (Box 11805)
  - Maxson, telefax (Box 11805)
  - Merchants (Box 11805)
  - Class interest (Box 11805)
  - S.U. Smith outlines (Box 11805)
  - Misc. notes (Box 11805)
  - Class outlines (Box 11805)
  - Oneida script (Box 11805)
  - Monday, Nov. 30, 1970 (Box 11805)
  - Oneida display (Box 11805)
  - Oneida display unit (Box 11805)
  - Oneida
    - Tray #179 (Box 11805)
    - Graphics (Box 11805)
    - Chest research and study (Box 11805)
    - Trays and chests stain flatware storage (Box 11805)
  - MDA brochure, 1969 (Box 11805)
  - Hazeltine Corp (Box 11805)
  - Unit span (Box 11805)
  - Human factors (Box 11805)
  - Human engineering (Box 11805)
  - Standards and v.e. (Box 11805)
  - Industrial design standards engineering (Box 11805)
  - MDA II type (Box 11805)
  - Dept. of City Planning, Syracuse (Box 11805)
- Box 11806
  - Story board (Box 11806)
  - IDSA
    - Design dialogue 3 (Box 11806)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1971-1974 (Box 11806)
    - Pocono (Box 11806)
  - Design study program (Box 11806)
  - IBA march (Box 11806)
  - Patents (Box 11806)
  - Office misc. (Box 11806)
  - Dui (Box 11806)
  - Stearns and wheeler (Box 11806)
  - Aw meeting/text (Box 11806)
  - Oneida, Bob Reed, kitchen sys. (Box 11806)
  - Jerrold, 1975-1976 (Box 11806)
  - Remote control unit (Box 11806)
  - Ideas DMM (Box 11806)
  - Resume (Box 11806)
  - Potential (Box 11806)
  - Phlander, Corning toaster (Box 11806)
  - Weekly day timer, 1972-1973 (Box 11806)
  - Safeway verticar, notes (Box 11806)
  - Fire rescues (Box 11806)
  - Safeway verticar
    - Sketches (Box 11806)
    - Brochure/photos (Box 11806)
    - Clippings (Box 11806)
    - Newsprint and comments (Box 11806)
  - Hi-rise fire info. (Box 11806)
  - Alivator (Box 11806)
  - Oman engines (Box 11806)
  - Safeway verticar, June 1975 (Box 11806)
  - Fire, June 1975 (Box 11806)
  - Towering inferno (Box 11806)
  - Advertising (Box 11806)
  - Aircraft and early George Beck (Box 11806)
  - Art Center College (Box 11806)
  - Automobiles (Box 11806)
  - G.E. Avionic (Box 11806)
  - G.E. SST presentation design (Box 11806)
  - G.E. Optical display unit (Box 11806)
  - F-S optical sight model redesign (Box 11806)
  - Design awards (Box 11806)
  - Dwight enterprises (Box 11806)
  - Jerrold (Box 11806)
- Box 11807
  - Photographs and color transparencies (Box 11807)
- Box 11808
  - Beck's label, 'miscellaneous, correspondence, clients' (Box 11808)
  - Arthur's K. Beef (Box 11808)
  - Cazenovia College (Box 11808)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 11808)
  - Costello, Cooney and Fearon (Box 11808)
  - Digney, Marion (Box 11808)
  - Eagan Real Estate (Box 11808)
  - Edwards, Lincoln (Box 11808)
  - 5-9 shop, OCSB (Box 11808)
  - Guaranteed Parts Company, Incorporated (Box 11808)
  - Hodgdon, Dewey (Box 11808)
  - E. Hommel and Son (Box 11808)
  - IBM (Box 11808)
  - King and King architects (Box 11808)
  - Kiosk (Box 11808)
  - Laroche (Box 11808)
  - Linklaen house (Box 11808)
  - Lincoln house (Box 11808)
  - Lucy's (Box 11808)
  - Mackenzie, Smith, Lewis, Mitchell, Hughes (Box 11808)
  - Massachusetts mutual (Box 11808)
  - Maxson electronics (Box 11808)
  - Metropolitan Development Association (Box 11808)
  - Minnesota Hospital Service Association (Box 11808)
  - Ninos (Box 11808)
  - Oberdorfer (Box 11808)
  - Oneida Ltd. (Box 11808)
  - Onondaga Community College (Box 11808)
  - Onondaga County Savings Association (Box 11808)
  - Dr. William Peacher (Box 11808)
  - Park Lane Shoe (Box 11808)
  - 189 - OCSB brochure (Box 11808)
  - GAB brochure (Box 11808)
  - Film, negative and positives (Box 11808)
  - GAB resume folders (Box 11808)
  - Oneida, 1971-1972 (Box 11808)
  - Oberdorfer Pump Division (Box 11808)
- Box 11809
  - Cazenovia College (Box 11809)
  - G.E. Integrated circuit products department (Box 11809)
  - Oneida Ltd. (Box 11809)
  - Bristol Asprite System (Box 11809)
  - Merchants Bank (Box 11809)
  - Stearns and Wheeler notes (Box 11809)
  - Robson and Woese Incorporated (Box 11809)
  - ID Magazine proposal (Box 11809)
  - MDA report, directory and envelope (Box 11809)
  - Lipe, rollway (Box 11809)
  - Optical display unit (Box 11809)
  - Maxon sign (Box 11809)
  - Maxson logo (Box 11809)
  - Fone-fax (Box 11809)
  - Oneida (Box 11809)
  - Telemax (Box 11809)
  - Roast beef restaurant (Box 11809)
  - Titles, Fred (Box 11809)
  - Lincoln Bank, Fred (Box 11809)
  - Syracuse blue receipts (Box 11809)
  - Correspondence (Box 11809)
  - AIGA contest (Box 11809)
  - Charles Gourmet symbol (Box 11809)
  - Charles Gourmet packaging (Box 11809)
  - Five - 9 fashions (Box 11809)
- Box 11810
  - Stearn and Wheeler (Box 11810)
  - Brochure plans and misc. (Box 11810)
  - Square pulse bonder (Box 11810)
  - General purpose control department (Box 11810)
  - Misc. (Box 11810)
  - Thin film bonding control (Box 11810)
  - Accounting sheets (Box 11810)
  - Confidential, current monthly account sheets (Box 11810)
  - MDA booklets (Box 11810)
  - Public relations (Box 11810)
  - G.B., congratulations notes (Box 11810)
  - IDI, IDSA, ICSIA (Box 11810)
  - Insurance receipts (Box 11810)
  - GAB, personal/family (Box 11810)
  - James Parsons (Box 11810)
  - Naneese, Vernon Court (Box 11810)
  - Guy, Univ of Denver (Box 11810)
  - UDC, direct costs (Box 11810)
  - Beck's "to file" (Box 11810)
  - Proposals, gab (Box 11810)
  - George Beck brochures (Box 11810)
  - Day-time records, G.B. (Box 11810)
  - MDA, brochure mock-ups (Box 11810)
  - Jefferson Tower, Pres. Plaza Apartments (Box 11810)
  - Pres. Plaza publicity (Box 11810)
  - Raytheon (Box 11810)
  - Rochester school model #19 (Box 11810)
  - Dr. Stark and Connelly (Box 11810)
  - Sutton Real Estate (Box 11810)
  - Syracuse, 1980 (Box 11810)
  - Syracuse Dept. of City Planning (Box 11810)
  - United Parcel Service (Box 11810)
  - University Hill Corp. (Box 11810)
  - U.D.C. Folder (Box 11810)
  - Valley Sport Center (Box 11810)
  - Watt, Gordon (Box 11810)
  - Harry Ward Liquor Store (Box 11810)
  - White Tower Corporation
    - Syracuse butteries (Box 11810)
    - World buttery (Box 11810)
    - Misc. (Box 11810)
- Box 11811
  - Tv channel selector (Box 11811)
  - Photo albums (Box 11811)
  - Executive planner (Box 11811)
  - Appointment book, 1977 (Box 11811)
  - Photographs in briefcase (Box 11811)
  - Drawings (Box 11811)
  - Photo album (Box 11811)
  - Sketches of silverware (Box 11811)
  - Photos (Box 11811)
- Box 11812
  - Limelight magazine (Box 11812)
  - IDSA, 1965 (Box 11812)
  - National meeting, 1966 (Box 11812)
  - Board meeting minutes (Box 11812)
  - IDSA, national meeting (Box 11812)
  - IDI, Detroit, 1964 (Box 11812)
  - ICSID, Vienna Congress (Box 11812)
  - Pert (Box 11812)
  - IDSA, 1966 (Box 11812)
  - Design recognition (Box 11812)
  - Miscellaneous drawings (Box 11812)
  - House plans (Box 11812)
  - Drawing (Box 11812)
  - Photos (Box 11812)
  - General Electric folio (Box 11812)
  - Photos and drawings (Box 11812)
  - Portable cab (Box 11812)
  - Transmitter (Box 11812)
  - Coordinated unit cabinets (Box 11812)
  - Tone arms (Box 11812)
  - Table models (Box 11812)
  - Speciality division (Box 11812)
  - Record changer (Box 11812)
  - Radio/phono (Box 11812)
  - Advance (pub. mat.) (Box 11812)
  - Calendar, notes, correspondence (Box 11812)
  - Line console cabinets, 1952 (Box 11812)
  - G.E. Radio color (Box 11812)
  - Musaphonic by General Electric (Box 11812)
  - Sketches, period console (Box 11812)
  - Receipts, trip to europe (Box 11812)
  - Many photographs (Box 11812)
  - G.B. - G.E. correspondence, 1961 (Box 11812)
- Box 11813
  - Various drawings (Box 11813)
  - Architectural plans (Box 11813)
  - P. and A. Designs (Box 11813)
  - G.E. (Box 11813)
- Box 11814
  - International list of schools of design (Box 11814)
  - Various newsletters (Box 11814)
  - IDA award to Beck (Box 11814)
  - The HMED Look reprint (Box 11814)
  - Reprints from Industrial Design, 1965 (Box 11814)
  - Aluminum dinnerware (Box 11814)
  - Tableware contest (Box 11814)
  - 139 Oneida cutlery (Box 11814)
  - Oneida
    - Macy display (Box 11814)
    - Ltd. Showroom (Box 11814)
    - Discount (Box 11814)
    - Ltd. Modular chest stainless (Box 11814)
    - Ltd. P.T. Noyes (Box 11814)
    - Package, foamold (Box 11814)
  - Raytheon, electronic oven (Box 11814)
  - Party invitations (Box 11814)
  - Onondaga County Savings Bank (Box 11814)
  - Vads rate table (Box 11814)
  - G.E. F 4d sight test station (Box 11814)
  - G.E. Optical sight display (Box 11814)
  - Call for entries 9th annual wescon (Box 11814)
  - G.E. Avionic controls (Box 11814)
  - Gamble (Box 11814)
  - Albert's display lights (Box 11814)
  - J.V.H. Display (Box 11814)
  - Sako, Finland (Box 11814)
  - ID Magazine, Sako (Box 11814)
  - Minnesota hospital (Box 11814)
  - Pres. Plaza
    - Modifications (Box 11814)
    - Lobby fountain (Box 11814)
    - General (Box 11814)
  - Bristol Labs (Box 11814)
  - Bristol (Box 11814)
  - Time capsule (Box 11814)
  - Valley Sport Center (Box 11814)
  - Fairmont Fair (Box 11814)
  - Fairmont Fair Landscape (Box 11814)
  - Green Giant (Box 11814)
  - Lincoln Bank
    - Rendering (Box 11814)
    - Tellers counters (Box 11814)
    - Signs (Box 11814)
    - Directory and display area (Box 11814)